This time around, the Batten Girls' Squadron turned around and battened down the hatches.
A fan club tour in Indonesia with the members of the troop
A fan exchange event conceived by the members
The happening of the Akinator quiz with a 0.1% level of correct answers
This time, it's a quiz show with viewer participation!
Watch to the end!
Batten Girl Squad's Turn over Batten
Indonesia
Can I ask you to line them up a little?
This way!
Ready!
Indonesia!
Yeah!
Yi de ne shea!
First of all
I'm going to have a welcome party with the tour group right after this, and then I'm going to have a party with the tour group right after this.
So I'm in uniform today!
Oh, my gosh!
They are so cute!
And they even have a two-shot!
I see. So, you're going to play some games today, right?
Yes, we are.
At the welcome party, there will be a quiz,
We do things like quizzes, rock-paper-scissors, and handing out souvenirs,
This time, Kinnah came up with the idea.
This time, Kinnah came up with the idea of an acinator game.
There is a theme, and then you are asked a question,
We answer yes or no to the question,
We answer yes or no, and get closer and closer to the answer.
Yes.
The members decide the theme, and the members ask the questions.
The members who saw the game were told, "Wait a minute, wait a minute, you've been sneaking around,
Wait a minute, wait a minute, they keep sneaking around.
They were practicing just now.
I heard that this is your first time to be an Akinator.
Yes, it's my first time.
Ai-chan has never done a live performance before,
She's never done it before, but she'll be a questioner and a questioner,
It's pretty scary.
I'm looking forward to it.
Well, there is one team that I'm a little worried about.
I know, right?
I had a bad feeling.
But now that those two have come together,
I knew that the most outrageous answers would probably be solidified there.
It was like playing Bubba.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's right.
Those two definitely have it.
No doubt about it.
Right now.
They are the pair?
Yes, they are.
That's the problem. They're perfect. How did you decide on the pair?
Kuchigipa. Otherwise, you wouldn't be in this pair.
Are you sure you can handle it? I'll do my best. I'm going to be strong.
Yes, everyone, please come to Indonesia today. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I hope we can make many visits together.
I would like to say hello and say that skirts should be short,
But today, the members wore long skirts,
I think long skirts have their own advantages, don't they?
Let me tell you a little more.
We are performing at night tonight,
Let's eat a lot of food and dance well together.
So, cheers!
Cheers!
Yes, how did you like it?
Well, I was surprised.
I had an image of you making a toast.
Oh, really?
I just found out about it today.
Really? I thought.
I thought about it.
Okay, I'll go.
Hey!
Next time?
Oh, yes!
I was wondering about this dress.
Yes, I'll get it in Osaka.
Have you seen Mom?
She hasn't come to work yet.
I met her sister.
Also, there was a dress on sale, but I couldn't buy it.
Uncle!
As soon as I know the answer,
I want you all to answer.
If you answer, I'd like you to raise your hand when you know the answer.
Members can't answer the questions.
We'll ask the questions that the members want to ask.
I don't know if the questions you are looking for will be asked.
I'll have to think about it.
I've prepared for this.
The person who comes first may be rewarded.
Maybe...
Mister...
Yes, sir.
Food?
Oh, my God.
Would you like to see it? Young man.
It's hard, isn't it?
Is it a vegetable?
Partially, yes.
Yes, partially.
Is it a makunouchi bento?
No, it's not.
Yes, it is.
What's this?
Makunouchi.
I don't like it.
Have you eaten in the last month?
No, I haven't.
Wow.
But, uh, I'm not supposed to tell you.
Laughs.
Have you eaten in the last six months?
Yes, I have.
Cherry blossoms are your favorite food?
Yes, I do.
Do they look brown?
Yes, it is.
Brown.
It looks brown.
There are a lot of brown things.
Lots of brown.
Member, maybe you should be more specific.
I think I got it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
LOL!
LOL.
Let them cheer for the best.
Correct.
Eeeeee!
How did you know?
That's great!
Congratulations!
Congratulations.
Do I know you?
Yes, I do.
Are you a member of the Batten Shoes Club?
No, I'm not.
Are you a manager?
No.
Do you know anyone in the country?
Yes, sir.
Do you know the whole world?
Are you an idol?
No.
Do you have black hair?
Yes and no.
Yes, ma'am.
What is he now?
Debutante.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my gosh!
The one with the great hair was a debutante.
How did you know?
You have a great connection.
Yes, yes.
Euroness has something to do with Indonesia.
Oh, my God!
I heard it's the hardest problem you've ever had to solve, but I'm not sure if you're doing it.
I don't know, maybe it's just a different concept.
Yeah, it's scary...
Let's go.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
Is it food?
No, sir.
People?
Oh, wait, partially.
No.
Not exactly.
What do you think, Riryachan?
From Riryachan's point of view, it's a little different.
Different?
Yes, I do.
Character
Is he/she real?
No, he is not.
Yes, he is.
Have you seen them?
Well, well, well, well, that's not the concept.
It's not about seeing it or not seeing it when it's real.
It might as well be real.
Is it a living thing?
Yes, partially.
Partially.
Partial?
Do you all know it?
Language?
The word?
Yes.
Japanese?
Yes!
Hippo?
No, sir!
Yes!
Mermaid?
No, sir!
Yes!
No, sir.
I think we're all talking about you two.
It's not like they're real or anything.
I know the answer.
I know the answer. It's really simple.
I think I might have it.
Go ahead.
What the hell?
NO.
I guess it didn't fall out.
YEAH.
do you want to fly?
you want to fly?
For me, yeah.
Oh, my God, it's getting closer.
Should I be more specific?
I don't know. It's not that kind of poochie.
Pochon?
Yes, it is.
We didn't intend to be Pochon.
Yes, yes, yes.
Does this have something to do with Indonesia?
Yes!
You look happy.
We're getting closer.
Getting closer? Now.
We'll go where the excitement was.
The excitement?
Hmm?
What?
I can't even do one anymore.
What am I supposed to ask?
Can you give me a hint?
Hints?
It's got movement, doesn't it?
Okay.
What is it?
Can I give you a better hint?
No, thank you.
Mmm-hmm.
Mm-hmm.
Is it really that long?
Is there any chance you guys could see us in this situation right now?
No, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's like, when we landed, it was like, "Huh.
Oh, okay!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! Yeeeeeesssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssss
ệぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇ Тыぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇぇiaぇぇ isolate
cup ِ
YANS
effic b
Te qu
we
Oh, I thought you came?
No, I'm going. Se-no
Se-o, Indonesia, a new step forward, marching on!
So cute!
It's really cute, and this is Indonesia, a new step forward!
Japanese course YouTube
Wow!
Flying, you know, that one moment.
I flew here!
I flew from Indonesia!
I've flown!
You must be exhausted
Congratulations
Congratulations!
I'm still sold
My favorite thing about choral music is that it is the most natural. I love the naturalness of it, and I also love the music, the songs, and the performances.
I would like to introduce Kiina Haruno.
What do you like about Kiina?
The best thing about Kiina is that she is a hard worker. She tries her best in everything with a positive attitude. That is the best part.
How long have you been encouraging her?
Since we met, we have been in the space of F-Girls.
Yes, it's been a long time.
It's been a long time, but I guess the three of us are the ones who are really involved.
I'll say two.
Sakura Seta.
What do you like about Ms. Seta?
All of them.
She has a core, she's good, she's one of a kind.
She's thoughtful and considerate.
She is cool!
Here is the tour pass!
This T-shirt is awesome too!
Yes, it's a bonus for the tour!
This is Ai Kiyama.
What do you like about Ai?
I love her smile, she is always so energetic and full of smiles!
Oh, this is Miu Yanagi, and yes, she is my favorite!
What I like about Miu is that she is mature in some ways and cute in others.
She's a good singer, too, so it's fun to guess her.
By the way, who are you referring to?
Lira Aoi.
What do you like about Lira?
I like her hard work.
I think she is the most cute of all.
She always cheers me up.
I will live because of her.
What do you like about Gakuen Shoujo?
She's cute and her live performance is amazing!
Their live performance is amazing!
I love their musicality!
By the way, who do you like? Riko.
Weda Rico.
My favorite thing about Rico is
Her live performance!
She's so cool!
I love the gap between her cool look and her smiling face.
Also, the way you lead the group as an MC.
I can tell that you are a very strong person.
I love that about him!
Next time on Urabatten
The documentary series will start!
It's called
Project Manten
The next installment of
The documentary series
Project Manten